♪The phone number I remember by heart♪
♪ رقم الهاتف الذي أذكره في القلب ♪
♪You stopped answering all my calls♪
♪ لقد توقفت عن الإجابة على كل اتصالاتي ♪
♪Does it cause trouble for your new relationship♪
♪ هل يسبب مشكلة بعلاقتك الجديدة ♪
♪Those photos of us I kept♪
♪ تلك الصور لنا التي احتفظت بها ♪
♪I kept them because I wouldn't let go of the past♪
♪ احتفظت بها لأن لن أتخلى عن الماضي ♪
♪It was just a habit to cling to each moment♪
كانت مجرد عادة للاعتماد على كل لحظة ♪
=Captain Han=
= النقيب هان =
=Episode 21=
= الحلقة 21 =
(It's been ten years.)
(مر عشر سنوات)
(Coming back here, I realized)
(للعودة إلى هنا، أدركت)
(people have desires because they have love.)
(لدى الناس رغبات لأن لديهم الحب)
(And my love has always stayed here.)
(وحبي بقي دائما هنا)
♪I don't know how to make you stay♪
♪ لا أعرف كيف أجعلك تبقى ♪
Xu Nannan.
شو ناننان
♪The phone number I remember by heart♪
♪ رقم الهاتف الذي أذكره في القلب ♪
♪You stopped answering all my calls♪
♪ لقد توقفت عن الإجابة على كل اتصالاتي ♪
♪Does it cause trouble for your new relationship♪
♪ هل يسبب مشكلة بعلاقتك الجديدة ♪
♪Those photos of us I kept♪
♪ تلك الصور لنا التي احتفظت بها ♪
♪I kept them because I wouldn't let go of the past♪
♪ احتفظت بها لأن لن أتخلى عن الماضي ♪
Long time no see.
لم أرك منذ وقت طويل
♪Maybe I have no merits♪
♪ ربما ليس لدي مزايا ♪
♪I'm being stubborn♪
♪ أنا عنيدة ♪
♪I don't know how to make you stay♪
♪ لا أعرف كيف أجعلك تلتزم ♪
♪I remained silent as you turned away without hesitation♪
♪ التزمت الصمت كما رفضت دون تردد ♪
♪The phone number I remember by heart♪
♪ رقم الهاتف الذي أذكره في القلب ♪
♪You stopped answering all my calls♪
♪ لقد توقفت عن الإجابة على كل اتصالاتي ♪
♪Does it cause trouble for your new relationship♪
♪ هل يسبب مشكلة بعلاقتك الجديدة ♪
♪Those photos of us I kept♪
♪ تلك الصور لنا التي احتفظت بها ♪
♪I kept them because I wouldn't let go of the past♪
♪ احتفظت بها لأن لن أتخلى عن الماضي ♪
♪It was just a habit to cling to each moment♪
كانت مجرد عادة للتمسك بكل لحظة ♪
♪The phone number I remember by heart♪
♪ رقم الهاتف الذي أذكره في القلب ♪
♪You stopped answering all my calls♪
♪ لقد توقفت عن الإجابة على كل اتصالاتي ♪
♪Does it cause trouble for your new relationship♪
♪ هل يسبب مشكلة بعلاقتك الجديدة ♪
♪Those photos of us I kept♪
♪ تلك الصور لنا التي احتفظت بها ♪
♪I kept them because I wouldn't let go of the past♪
♪ احتفظت بها لأن لن أتخلى عن الماضي ♪
♪It was just a habit to cling to each moment♪
كانت مجرد عادة تعتمد على كل لحظة ♪
Welcome.
أهلا
Miss Xu, without you,
الآنسة شو، بدونك
our captain was pretty low.
كان القبطان لدينا منخفضا جدا
Really?
حقا؟
Fang Cheng.
فانغ تشنغ
Gross.
مقرف
Captain, we have to go.
أيها النقيب، علينا أن نذهب
Go.
اذهبي
These flowers...
هذه الأزهار...
They know you're back.
يعرفون أنك عدت
They bought them
اشتروها لك
for you.
لك
They treat me better than they treat you.
إنهم يعاملونني بشكل أفضل من الذين يعاملونك
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Don't move.
لا تتحركي
Come on.
هيا
(Pay for what you did. Ricin will take you to where you belong.)
ادفعن ما فعلته سيأخذك الريسين إلى حيث تنتمين)
Hold your breath, and don't move.
و لا تتحرك
Captain.
قائد
Back off.
تراجع
Call an ambulance.
اتصل بالإسعاف
Quick.
بسرعة
This powder is toxic, isn't it?
هذا المساحيق سام أليس كذلك
Don't be scared. Do as I say.
لا تكن خائفًا، افعل ما أقول
You'll be fine.
ستكونين بخير
Han Xizhou.
هان شي تشو
You haven't touched much.
لم تتأثري كثيرا
You get out quickly. Don't stay here with me.
اخرجا بسرعة لا تبق هنا معي
No way. I told you.
مستحيل، قلت لك
No matter what happens,
مهما حدث
I will always be there.
سأكون دائما هناك
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Ricin powder.
مسحوق الأرز
It can remain in the human body for several hours.
يمكن أن يظل في الجسم البشري لعدة ساعات
Han Xizhou.
هان شي تشو
We can't move?
لا يمكننا التحرك؟
My hands go numb.
ليس لدي أرقام
Hold on.
انتظر
It's from Cheng Dahai, right?
إنه من تشنغ داهاي، صحيح؟
This is probably fake.
هذه مزيفة على الأرجح
This stuff is hard to find.
هذه الأشياء يصعب العثور عليها
Whether it's real or fake,
سواء كانت حقيقية أم مزيفة
at least I saw you.
على الأقل رأيتك
So, I have no regrets.
لذا لا أندم
Okay, don't talk anymore.
حسنًا لا تتحدثي
Thankfully, it's not ricin.
لحسن الحظ، ليس رائعا
False alarm.
إنذار خاطئ
Xiya, how is he? Is he awake?
يا شيا، كيف حاله؟ هل استيقظ؟
He got a cut on his leg yesterday.
قطع ساقه أمس
Today it's even worse.
اليوم الأمر أسوأ
But it has been stitched.
لكنه تم صلب الموضوع
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm okay.
أنا بخير
That is not ricin at all.
هذه ليست رائحة على الإطلاق
Cheng Dahai just fooled us.
تشنغ داهاي خدعنا فقط
The police are handling it.
الشرطة تتولى الأمر
They let him go after a warning.
تتركيه يذهب بعد تحذير
Why did you pull out the needle?
لماذا سحبت الإبرة؟
You haven't finished the fluids yet.
لم تنه السوائل بعد
Does it hurt?
هل هذا مؤلم؟
Yes.
نعم
I'll call Xiya over.
سأتصل بشيا
Don't leave.
لا تغادر
Nannan, since you left,
ننان، منذ أن غادرت
my heart has been aching.
لقد كان قلبي يخفق
♪Out of my own will♪
♪ خارج إرادي ♪
♪Be it sunny or rainy♪
♪ كن مشوشا أو ماطلا ♪
♪Further and further away♪
♪ مزيد من المسافة ♪
♪The dusk extends deeper♪
♪ الغبار ممتد بعمق ♪
♪After all these years♪
♪ بعد كل هذه السنوات ♪
♪My look won't expose my longing♪
♪ مظهرني لن يفضح شقتي ♪
♪I've never changed♪
♪ لم أتغير أبدا ♪
♪Wish all your dreams come true♪
♪ هل تتحقق كل أحلامك ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪I've been obsessed with you once♪
♪ لقد كنت مهووسة بك مرة واحدة ♪
♪Freedom is my customized label♪
♪ الحرية هي بطاقة التعريف الخاصة بي ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪Your smile fades away with time♪
♪ ابتسامتك تتلاشى مع الوقت ♪
♪Seeing you going away with her♪
♪ أمنحك بالخروج معها ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪I've been obsessed with you once♪
♪ لقد كنت مهووسة بك مرة واحدة ♪
♪Freedom is my customized label♪
♪ الحرية هي بطاقة التعريف الخاصة بي ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪Your smile fades away with time♪
♪ ابتسامتك تتلاشى مع الوقت ♪
♪Seeing you going away with her♪
♪ سيأخذك بعيدا معها ♪